[Mizuki grunts]
Damn it. You can totally see
my binder in this dress!
-[screams]
-No.
I just felt
my soul leave my body.
There's no way I can take
this stupid thing off.
But I can't exactly
keep it on either.
-[YAO] How's it fit, Ashiya?
-Uh?
Do you think we'll need
to adjust the length a little?
[MIZUKI] Actually, I don't.
Looks like it's about right.
Great to hear.
So, I can mark
Ashiya's dress as good to go.
[MIZUKI]
There's no other choice.
I'll just have to go
"au natural!"
-We were waiting for-- Uh?
-Uh?
[NANBA] Wow,
you pull that off well.
[MIZUKI] Fingers crossed!
Please, let me
get away with this!
I can't believe how much
you look like a real woman.
You could have fooled me.
[Mizuki chuckles nervously]
[NAKAO] That padded bra
certainly understood
-the assignment.
-[chuckles] I guess.
[SANO] Here, these are yours.
Oh, thanks.
So you're the shoe guy?
Funny job.
They asked me to help
if I had the time.
-And, uh...
-[MIZUKI] Uh?
...by the way...
that dress looks good on you.
[Mizuki gasps]
Whoa, did he just flirt with me?
My ears are on fire.
I'm such a dork.
-[KANNA] Hey, Mizuki.
-Uh?
For you. These are the stockings
you'll wear for the dance.
Here you go.
[MIZUKI] What's up?
There's something different
about you.
Huh? Oops.
Guess I'm an open book.
Oh, come on, Kanna.
You know you can trust me.
I don't know. I shouldn't!
Okay, I'll tell you.
Yesterday, Megumi asked me
to be his dance partner
at the ball.
Wow, Kanna, that's incredible.
Nice going, gorilla boy.
-[Tennoji sneezes]
-Uh?
How to put this?
It's such a delicate affair.
I think you've got a real shot
at being crowned queen.
[speaking German]
[in English] I beg you,
would you care to dance wi--
Get lost, you creep.
But... [speaking in German]
[Kanna gasps]
Oh, beautiful raven-haired
mistress of the dark sky,
would you care to--
Get your grubby paws
off her now!
Kanna is my blushing fiancée,
you got that, you fool?
[all gasp]
[ALL] Whoa!
[HIMEJIMA] What in the eff?
[♪ opening theme song playing]
I'M SO HAPPY!
[MIZUKI] And then...
he goes and spills all the beans
in front
of every single person there.
Amazing. You should have seen
the look on his face after that.
[laughs]
I'm surprised she'd go
for a meathead like him.
-She's so nice.
-Right?
Time flies.
Tomorrow's the big day, huh?
Yeah, I guess it is.
[MIZUKI] Say no if you want,
but I was wondering
if I could ask you a huge favor.
[SANO] Yeah, what?
It's just... I was hoping
you'd dance with me,
right now.
[gasps nervously]
I really asked him.
-Sure, why not?
-[gasps]
♪
[Mizuki gasps]
[SANO] And a-one...
[both grunt]
[thudding]
♪
[breathes softly]
[exhales softly]
♪
Awesome, that helped, thanks!
I'd better hit the sack!
Good night!
[panting]
I need to calm down.
[HIBARI] Let me welcome you,
ladies and gentlemen.
Tonight, we uphold
a time-honored tradition
between St. Blossom
and Osaka High.
Dance the night away and enjoy
yourselves to the fullest.
Why is she the only one who gets
to wear a special dress?
-Talk about a rigged game.
-[chuckles]
♪
-[Nakatsu gasps]
-[SANO] Hmm?
Hello there.
[MIZUKI] Wow! Okay, tuxedo Sano
is, like, gorgeous.
SLAM
Mizuki, you look
so freaking cute!
-[thumps]
-[Nakatsu grunts]
But it's true.
That dress looks red hot on you.
It's crazy how real
your boobs look.
[Mizuki chuckles]
They'd better look real.
You're looking
pretty sharp yourself. Uh?
Uh?
Huh?
[♪ ballroom music playing]
[MIZUKI] You're kidding.
It's like
something out of a fairy tale!
Aw, man.
All of a sudden,
I feel like a big dork
in cosplay or something.
I know exactly what you mean.
[BOY 1] Please share
this dance with me?
I came to ask the same.
Oh, no,
whatever is a girl to do?
[MIZUKI] Surprise, surprise.
Looks like one of us
is blending in just fine.
There's Nanba.
[KADOMA] He's swarmed by girls,
as usual.
I'd bet big money
those pests get eradicated
in 0.5 seconds.
Just what do you mean by that?
[MIZUKI] Stand back and watch.
There's my dashing prince!
[evil chuckle]
[MIZUKI] Told you.
I wonder where Sano ran off to.
[HIMEJIMA] Hello,
my sweet little lambs.
[both groan softly]
♪
[speaking in German]
[both groan]
[in English] This is a warning.
If you boys keep dressing
like yummy little tarts,
you might just get snatched up
and eaten by the big bad wolf.
[Kujo fake laughs]
It doesn't sound
like a joke coming from you.
Don't startle me!
You know I'm jumpy!
[BOTH] Kujo's such a good guy!
Listen,
this one's my dance partner,
so don't bug him.
That's my job this evening.
Hey, since we're both here,
wanna practice the dance
with me?
[KADOMA] Oh...
Sure. And osu!
[MIZUKI]
You can't just whip out
the karate stuff
dressed like that.
[girls exclaim] Handsome Oscar!
[speaking German]
-[in English] Please.
-[Mizuki sighs]
[RIO] Hey, there you are.
I've been looking
all over the ballroom for you.
-Hi, Rio.
-Where've you been tonight?
You weren't
in the changing room earlier.
Oh, right. I don't know.
I had to change in the bathroom.
Kanna gave me this
to give to you.
Huh? What is it?
Hold still for a sec.
Everyone's already
wearing theirs,
but you weren't around,
so...
There. All done!
Those flowers look
so sweet on you, Mizuki!
If I didn't know any better,
I would think you were
really a girl.
Oh, yeah? Well, that's silly.
[Rio sighs]
I'm sorry.
Why? Is something wrong?
I feel sort of bad
that I got paired up with Sano.
[gasps]
[yelps]
Sorry I know your secret.
As Umeda's little sister,
I get all the hot gossip.
It's hard when the person
you have a crush on
is, like, the hottest guy, huh?
Bet you've gotta
watch him like a hawk.
What?
I caught a glimpse of Sano
out in the crowd.
He was being swarmed by girls.
He kept trying to get away.
[Mizuki gasps] Yeah,
that sounds like him.
[RIO] I feel for you, Mizuki,
I do.
I've been around the block
with my bro,
so I've got no problem
with this kind of stuff.
Uh, okay.
[RIO] Good luck!
I'm rooting for you!
See you later!
[MIZUKI]
You have no idea whatsoever.
[groans]
So, the girls
are flocking to him?
[NAKATSU] Hey, Mizuki,
I was looking for you.
[MIZUKI] Uh?
What's with the mopey face,
my friend?
[MIZUKI] It's nothing.
Would you like to dance,
my queen? With me?
[Mizuki chuckles]
-Sounds fun.
-[Nakatsu gasps]
♪
[both chuckle]
[NAKATSU] Crap, I can't help it.
I know I shouldn't,
but I keep staring!
Is it even my fault
when they look that real?
-[MIZUKI] Uh, Nakatsu?
-[gasps]
Right here.
Check it out. Looks like
Hibari's gonna dance now.
[NAKATSU] Oh.
Wonder how those bazoombas
are gonna move
on the dance floor.
Oh, no!
Now that I've noticed them,
they're all I can think about.
Control yourself, soldier.
Forget aboob it... Crap!
Boobies!
Oh, my gosh, are you okay?
Whoa, what's wrong
with him, Ashiya?
I think Hibari's sex appeal was
too much for him and he fainted.
Lost lots of blood, too.
[NAKATSU] Kill me!
[MIZUKI] Is he going to be okay?
[splashes]
[Rio gasps] Mizuki!
Oh, no! Your dress is soaked.
Who'd do such a mean thing?
[BOY] That's low.
-[GIRL] What a shame. Poor girl.
-[Mizuki groans]
Guess they got me.
-[SANO] Ashiya.
-Uh?
[MIZUKI] Sano.
Man, that was completely
uncalled for.
Did anyone see who did it?
[RIO] No, but they purposefully
ruined his dress.
It's fine, I'm okay! I promise.
I'll go try and wash it out now.
Please, just give me one moment.
[SANO] Wait.
[MIZUKI] How embarrassing.
I don't want Sano
to see me like this.
[water splashing]
[MIZUKI] It's still stained.
I won't cry, though,
-not over this.
-[door opens]
-[RIO] How's it look?
-Uh?
[MIZUKI] No luck. It's ruined.
But it is what it is, so...
[YUMEMI] That stain's set.
Wow, it sure is,
and it looks like
a really gnarly one, too.
We can fix this.
Just let us take care of it.
[MIZUKI] Uh...
Sure. Thanks.
[ANNOUNCER] And now
the highlight of the night.
Find your partners.
This dance will decide
our king, queen,
and best couple of the year.
[♪ ballroom music playing]
[NIHONBASHI]
The dance might be a huge drag,
but my camera can always
handle the exposure! [giggles]
I know I didn't get a date
but why am I the one
stuck dancing with Nakao?
Dancing with any other guy
than the one and only Nanba
is a dagger to my heart!
You know,
I actually have feelings, too.
♪
[MIZUKI]
They fixed my dress for me,
but my dance partner
was medically evacuated.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gents,
it's officially our last dance
of the night.
[Mizuki gasps]
[MIZUKI] I'm still a part
of a fancy Christmas ball.
Might as well make the best
of it and have some fun.
♪
[RIO] Uh?
[SANO] Ashiya.
If you're that worried about him
then you should go check in.
-Huh?
-I promise
that I'm okay on my own.
You better hurry,
or someone else might
steal him from you.
Pardon me.
[chuckles]
[MIZUKI] Uh? Sano?
Uh?
Huh? Sano?
Mm...
[SANO] I want to dance with you.
Being a wallflower
is no fun at all.
Yeah, but I thought...
[RIO] Go. Go. Go.
Go. Go. Go. Go!
[SANO] So, what do you say?
You still feel like dancing?
I do. I really do.
[gasps]
Me too.
[Mizuki breathes softly]
-Here we go.
-Mm...
Don't look away.
-Wait, I can't do this.
-Why can't you?
I'm all red! Everyone will see
and think we're acting weird.
-Dummy, that doesn't matter.
-[breathes softly]
It's only one little dance.
That's no biggie, right?
♪
[chuckles softly]
[Yumemi exclaims] Aw, look.
[KANNA] My... how precious.
In my eyes, dear,
you're 100 times more precious!
Oh, my goodness,
those two are crushing it!
They look like
the perfect couple.
You'll trip
if you let your eyes wander.
♪
[HIBARI] My, look
at that hummingbird go.
This is going to be
a much tougher competition
than we thought.
Too bad for them.
My thoughts exactly.
[HIBARI] Face it, Hibari!
Dancing with him is the only way
to show the world
you're not just beautiful,
but talented!
[HIMEJIMA]
You must endure, Oscar.
Dancing with her is the only way
to show the world
your true grace and skill!
It'll be over
before you know it.
[ANNOUNCER] May I have
your attention, please?
It's time to announce
this year's lucky winners
-selected by your votes.
-This doesn't concern us.
-You wanna get lost?
-You know it.
[ANNOUNCER] We will begin
by announcing our queen.
[MIZUKI] Do you mind
waiting here for one sec?
[SANO] Mm.
Hm?
[MIZUKI] Surprise, it's for you.
What is it?
[chuckles] Well, tomorrow
is your birthday, isn't it?
I may be a whole day early,
but I got you a little
something-something.
♪
Somehow, the big day
slipped my mind last year.
So, this year,
I swore it wouldn't.
I wanted to be the first
to wish you happy birthday.
[SANO] Huh.
♪
[MIZUKI] Uh?
Wait, is this snow?
This is so cool!
It's snowing, Sano.
[SANO] You're like a little kid.
This is my first time
seeing snow.
What the heck do you want
from me? It's awesome.
-[SANO] Seriously?
-Seriously.
It's so cold.
Whoa, it melts so fast. Ah...
[Sano chuckles softly]
You're going to
catch a cold, goober.
[MIZUKI] Uh?
[Mizuki chuckles]
Happy birthday to you, Sano.
[SANO] Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[Umeda sighs]
[exhales]
Looks like it's going to stick.
[AKIHA] You need someone
to warm you up?
-Hello, Doctor!
-You're kidding!
What are you even doing here?
Let go of me!
[Akiha laughs]
It's almost Christmas.
Can Santa's good boy
crash at your place?
[UMEDA] Absolutely not.
[barks]
-[massager buzzing]
-So relaxing.
Are you for real?
Wasn't that supposed
to be my birthday present?
[chuckles]
But I can't stop myself.
[Sano sighs]
I may be a whole day early,
but I got you
a little something.
[SANO] An ultrasonic massager!
Kinda geriatric.
They're usually 15,000 yen,
but I found this one
for only 4,000. [chuckles]
Who cares how much it cost?
It was more than worth
the money I spent on it.
[Sano chuckles]
I told you, I love it.
Thanks a lot.
[Mizuki gasps, exclaims]
He put his chin on my shoulder.
I can't even
-think straight now.
-[phone vibrates]
JULIA
Julia's calling me.
Mizuki! Who wants some taiyaki?
[gasps]
-I do.
-Yay, I want some too.
CLINGY
[Nakatsu chuckles]
Normally, I'd come in
with my patented
"get your hands off
Mizuki tackle,"
but that's the old me.
I'm a brand-new man now.
Watch out, cause I'm manning up
to the max!
Prepare yourselves to be amazed:
it's the Super Macho
Nakatsu Revolution!
Wait! Your heart
will skip a beat for me--
Hey, Julia, what's going on
with you?
[Nakatsu screams]
Oh, you know me, I'm chilling.
Do you have a quick sec
to spill some tea?
I wanna get the deets
on what happened at the ball.
Uh? [chuckles]
We'll talk later.
Hi. It's been way too long,
Little Miss America.
And I see you're still
as annoying as ever,
you big, dumb ape. Get bent.
Just who do you think you are?
-[NANBA] Hey, guys.
-[ALL] Mm?
My grandma gave me some tickets
to the ice-skating rink.
Anyone wanna go?
[BOTH] Oh, hell yeah!
Is that creeper there?
Sounds like you've missed me.
It's been months
since you've had to leave, love,
and you have no idea
-how lonely I've been--
-Uh? She hung up.
[Nakatsu chuckles]
♪
[both exclaiming]
Hey, Nakatsu, what're you doing
by yourself over there, huh?
-Let's goof off together!
-Yeah, yeah, I hear you.
Hey, everyone,
check out this dork on ice
-who can't skate!
-[both chuckle]
Can it, morons.
Kansai people don't ice skate!
Get me on skis or a snowboard
in the Lake Biwa valley
and watch me shred!
I can even ski blindfolded,
I'll have you know!
Being able to skate
with his legs akimbo
is a talent all its own.
[KAYASHIMA] Looks like
Ashiya's a real natural.
[SANO]
Just like a fish in the water.
[Nakatsu grunts]
He's not the only fish.
Look who else is totally
in their element on the ice.
Oh, my gosh,
you're from that PuPa ad.
I'd recognize you anywhere!
[GIRL 2] Wow, you look
even hotter in person!
He's wearing the coat
from the shoot.
What a sad little
attention whore.
He's resorting to smoke
and mirrors, I see.
-There's my favorite guy.
-[Nanba gasps]
Don't forget you promised me
that we would hold hands
while we skate together.
You're such a naughty boy.
[GIRLS] Whoa, we give up.
[NAKAO] Come with me, darling.
[sighs] Well,
I guess this is my life now.
Did you see that?
Nakao's got real game.
What a genius move.
That was so cunning
and calculated,
those girls had no clue
they were being played.
[MIZUKI] Hey,
what you guys talking about?
Yeah, I know.
Nakao has chosen
quite a difficult path in life.
After all,
ever since Nanba
was crowned king,
the competition has been stiff.
[NAKATSU] So, the players
gotta get smart.
Did anybody else think
that Hibari was a lot?
What, she's perfect!
She totally deserved
to be crowned queen!
Okay, that's not what I meant.
[GIRLS] Hail Hibari!
Hail Hibari!
Well, you know, I'm convinced
they rigged the votes
so that only one of the
St. Blossom girls would win.
Mm-hmm. Honestly, I thought
Ashiya was way prettier
than all those Blossom girls.
My new rival.
[laughs] That's very sweet
of you, but get real.
What? I don't get it. I mean...
you two won the special award
for best couple.
[MIZUKI] Oh, yeah.
That was kinda amazing.
I never thought I'd win an award
with the Izumi Sano!
That's true.
But it's not like
that was a super official award
or anything.
Tennoji and Kanna
were the happy duo
that won
the real best couple award.
[Nakatsu cries]
I've only got myself to blame!
I'm such a stupid loser.
If only I hadn't passed out
on the dance floor,
Mizuki and I could've
easily won that award!
-Dummy.
-Huh?
-Kyomi?
-Hm.
Hey, cutie,
what are you doing here?
Kyomi, I said
don't let go of my hand.
[Nakatsu chuckles] Kagurazaka?
Well, look at you over here,
being the perfect big brother.
Sorry? The hell are you
even talking about?
-[TAMAMI] Sister attack!
-Tamami came to skate, too?
Wait, what?
-We haven't seen you in ages!
-[speaking indistinctly]
That's right.
[Tamami gasps]
What a co-inky dink!
It's so good to see you, Mizuki.
And what's up, Izumi?
You're going
to the next meet, right?
I'll be cheerin' for you!
See you later!
Me too. You better not get
some lame-ass score though.
I'll try my best.
[KAGURAZAKA] Well, let's go.
High five me first.
-[KYOMI] Uh?
-[NAKATSU] Atta girl!
[MIZUKI] You're kidding.
Rio's parents are here!
Oh, my!
You two sure look like
you're having a good time.
[SEIRA] You know it.
The tickets expire today.
Wait, that would make them
Dr. Umeda's folks too, right?
[NAKATSU] They're in their 50s.
Must have discovered
the fountain of youth.
[NAKAO] Nanba, wait for me.
I wanna slow skate some more.
Hold on. I'd know that
shaggy head anywhere!
Is that you, Minami?
Wait, what?
You guys are here too.
Hey, Grandma and Gramps.
Grandma?
And you call him Gramps?
-[BOTH] But she's so young.
-[BOTH] And so is he.
[ALL] Nanba's their grandson?
Then that would mean Io is...
-And Umeda is...
-That would make Rio his...
-What's up, guys?
-Lost in your thoughts?
Not quite. Just family math.
Somehow, Rio's Nanba's aunt.
[MIZUKI]
The cat's out of the bag!
-I'm so sorry, Rio!
-[SEKIME] Aunt? His aunt?
[SEIRA] Oh, come on, Minami.
How many times
do I have to ask you
to call us Mama Seira
and Papa Azuma?
[AZUMA] My darling.
Let me hold you.
[gasps]
Oh, Azuma, hon!
[ALL] Aw, they're
still lovebirds.
Just in case you boys forgot,
those two won
the best couple award
at the joint ball
back in their day.
[MIZUKI] Dr. Umeda said
whoever gets voted best couple
supposedly lives
happily ever after.
I can't just write it off
as superstition
after witnessing
the two of them together.
[both gasp]
Close call, but I got you.
[MIZUKI] Thank you.
[SANO] You have to be
extra careful.
It's really slippery
at the edge of the rink.
-Come on, let's go around again.
-Huh?
[grunts]
[NAKATSU] Hey!
What am I, chopped liver?
♪
[MIZUKI] Maybe a bit of
the superstition will rub off.
I mean, we did win
best couple, after all.
[Sano exhales]
[Mizuki chuckles softly]
♪
[Mizuki chuckles]
I've never been
this happy before.
That's got everything
to do with him.
I hope Sano and I
are always together.
[♪ closing theme song playing]